♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in
movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
We now return to the extended
director's cut
of Willy Wonka and the
Chocolate Factory.
♪ ♪
Charlie, don't forget
what happened to the boy
- who got everything he ever wanted.
- What?
He lived happily ever after.
But he did have to earn it.
Hint, hint.
Do it, Charlie!
I'm not going back
to that four-person bed!
Hell, I'll do it, if you want!
No! It has to be a child!
What did he just say?
Brian, this does not seem appropriate
to watch in front of the baby.
Not appropriate?
You took me to see Magic Mike XXL.
Uhp, this one's wet.
Uh, this one, too.
Also wet.
Huh. This one's dry,
but the back of the
seat in front of it is wet.
Let's put on
something more child-friendly.
Time to "Too-tooty-too"
with The Turtlenecks!
Oh, God, no. These guys are horrible.
♪ Do you kazoo? ♪
♪ I often do ♪
♪ When I am blue ♪
♪ I do kazoo ♪
♪ Tootooty-Too ♪
♪ Goes my kazoo ♪
♪ I will kazoo ♪
♪ Hey how 'bout you? ♪
Uch. All they're doing
is announcing that they play the kazoo,
and then asking if others
also play the kazoo.
This doesn't seem so bad.
I mean, after all,
it's a song for babies.
Yeah, but-but that's the thing.
Baby songs never tackle
real baby issues.
You know, like... like loud noises.
Or teething.
Or when Dad uses me as a lumbar pillow.
- Eh...
- Ow.
- Ow. Ow.
Ow.
This thing works better in the car.
Well, how could they
address baby issues?
Children's songs are written by adults.
And, dollars to donuts, white adults.
I-I.. Who-who are
you mad at, Brian?
Uch, how much time you got?
Not enough for that, but you're right.
If you want a song a baby'll like,
you've got to get a baby to write it.
Well, call John Mayer.
He's a big, fat baby.
No, I'll do it, and you can help.
Well, I... I did write
a musical about Alexander Hamilton.
Not-not that one,
but, uh, sure, I'm in.
Ooh, I'm excited.
This'll be great.
And those guys back at
the factory can suck it.
I'm gonna get out of this place one day.
Hey, Butch.
Get a load of Stewie.
He says he's gonna get out of here.
You don't know me, man. I'm different.
I got ideas.
Hey, Butch, you hear that?
Stewie's got ideas.
Shut up!
I'm gonna go across that river
and make it to the city
on the other side.
I'm gonna be a singer.
Bubl├й over here says
he's gonna be a singer.
Hey, Bubl├й, I got a
tune for you to sing.
It's called "Get Your Ass Back
on the Forklift, Lunch is Over".
Hey, Stewie, don't listen to those guys.
Follow your heart.
Shut up, Butch.
You're the loser of this crew.
Hey guys, you hear that?
Butch told me to follow my heart.
Dad, can I have 50 bucks
for a shamrock tattoo?
It's time.
All right, but make sure you get it
where everyone can see.
Hold on, Peter.
I-if Chris wants money for something,
maybe it's time he got a part-time job.
He could mow lawns or-or babysit.
I can't work.
I'm too young.
Well, Will Smith's little kid
works as a movie star,
even though he looks
like a wet baby horse.
All right, I suppose I could get a job.
Well, maybe even my old job as the guy
racing through an airport
at the end of a romantic comedy.
Taxi! Taxi!
Hey. Are you crazy?
Crazy for love.
The most amazing girl I've ever met
leaves on a plane in five minutes.
Get in.
What the hell's going on?
This guy's in love.
Is she worth it?
She's a once-in-a-life-time girl.
I'll give you an escort.
No charge.
Final boarding call for Ashley's flight
to stuffy New England college.
Final boarding.
Ooh, whoa, whoa, whoa, child.
What's the hurry?
The love of my life, that's what.
We got a code Romeo.
Repeat, code Romeo.
If you get there on time,
there's an extra 50 in it for you.
I love this job!
Ashley, wait!
I wouldn't miss this for all
the rush hour fares in Bigtown.
Chris, you came. Oh, my God!
Let me get my grandma.
Chris?
Ashley. I love you.
Oh, you're groaning at me?
You paid $19 to fly Spirit Air.
You get what you get.
All right, Brian,
I've written a few songs,
all about stuff babies
actually care about.
No more rainbows and unicorns.
Real baby issues.
Right, like heartworm and parvo?
No, baby stuff.
Oh, oh, human babies.
I didn't... I didn't realize
there was an agenda.
Okay, look, just pay attention.
♪ Momma liked to party
when you were in her belly ♪
♪ Drinking, she did some ♪
♪ Momma liked to party
when you were in her belly ♪
♪ That's why you are dumb. ♪
I call that "Momma Liked to Party".
Stewie, that's good.
Hey, can I write one?
Yeah, we need as many as we can.
Our first gig is Saturday.
It's a birthday party.
Wow, already?
How'd you book a gig so fast?
Easy. I figured out the perfect way
to get the word out
to middle-aged moms.
Musical entertainment,
available for parties.
Hey. Where you drinking that Chardonnay?
Oh, hey, Chris,
how's the job hunt going?
Terrible. I can't find a job anywhere.
A lot of people seem to be turned off
by my dishonorable discharge.
What, from the Army?
No, it's a euphemism.
Oh, yucky.
Uh, you guys, I need help
unloading the groceries.
My undiagnosed mom injury is flaring up.
These little things of applesauce
better not be for desserts.
Go to hell, Glenn Quagmire!
I'm sorry, but Mondays are Asian only.
Why is your last name Wong?
It's my married name.
Now I see why you're here.
Geez, what was that about?
Ah, a little scheduling mix-up.
I am just so busy,
I-I don't have any time
to organize my own life.
Wait a minute, what if you had someone
to help keep you organized?
Chris is looking for work.
Maybe he can help you
out, be your assistant.
Huh, maybe.
You have any references?
Uh, "cowabunga," "schwing,"
"yada, yada, yada."
Those are pretty good references.
You're hired.
Look at that. Look at the cake.
"Happy Birthday Charlie
and Uncle Craig."
And Uncle Craig's written
in a different color.
Oh, poor Uncle Craig.
Hey, is that your
ex-girlfriend, Olivia?
God, what's she doing here?
She was always such a nightmare.
Olivia?! Oh, my God, do I look okay?
I hate this shirt.
Switch shirts. Switch shirts!
Stewie? Oh, I thought that was you.
Hey, Olivia, hey, what brings you here?
Oh, the birthday boy and I met
at Burt Reynolds' acting
camp in Jupiter, Florida.
Well, I'm glad to hear
you're still acting.
You know, the last time
I saw you, you were...
Burning in a cardboard house?
Yeah, burning in a cardboard
house, yeah.
Uh, hey, listen, uh, I don't
know if you've heard,
but we're the entertainment.
Aw, that's good. Good for you.
Okay, great to see you.
Come on, Stewie, it's not about her.
It's about those six
children watching and the spazzy kid
who's just waiting for the snakes.
Bring out the snakes!
It's a hot crowd, have fun out there.
I'm gonna go feed everything
in my van to each other.
Okay, kids, if
everyone's done washing their hands
from the snakes, we
have some fun music for y...
No climbing on the boat!
Okay, now please welcome
Red Shirt Blue Shirt.
All right, we're Red Shirt Blue Shirt,
and here's a song we call
"Mommy and Daddy's Room."
And we think it's one
you can all relate to.
♪ When everybody's gone to sleep ♪
♪ And you've said good night moon ♪
♪ There's plenty of
noise still coming ♪
♪ From Mommy and Daddy's room ♪
♪ Oh, Daddy says "please,"
Mommy says "no" ♪
♪ Daddy says "come
on," Mommy says "whoa" ♪
♪ Daddy goes... , Mommy goes "ow" ♪
♪ Daddy says "I'm
done," Mommy goes "wow" ♪
♪ Daddy rolls over
and falls asleep ♪
♪ Mommy drinks wine in the dark. ♪
My God, did you hear 'em,
Stewie? We're a hit.
We got to go out and celebrate.
Oh, he can't go out with you tonight.
He's got a date with me.
Really? Awesome.
Brian, I can't go. I'm not feeling well.
Stewie, I've been
standing here the whole time.
But, you know-you know
what, that's fine.
I'll just go have a dog-style
celebration by myself.
Yeah!
Awesome time!
This is very fun for me!
- Hey!
- Oh, hey!
- This is fun, right?
- The best!
And me, too!
Great crowd, babe.
What are... What is this?
Oh, Olivia's president of our fan club.
She's also doing half the band.
Do you even know what that means?
Uh, let's just say I couldn't
toddle right for a week.
Okay, you don't.
All right, if you'll excuse me,
I have a poo poo diaper.
You really think this
Olivia thing is a good idea?
Why wouldn't it be?
I don't know. It just seems like
it always ends badly for you two.
And it can be tricky working with an ex.
Look at Kermit and Miss Piggy.
How are you feeling, Miss Piggy?
I heard you called in sick yesterday.
Yeah, I had a frog in my throat.
Right, Kermie?
Eh? Right?
Please stop drinking.
Okay, Chris, I think you're
gonna be a great assistant.
Your paperwork appears to be in order,
but before we get started, do you own
a pair of rubber boots
that you'd have to wear
if you worked on a fishing boat?
Uh, no, I don't think so.
All right, I guess
it'll be a light day today,
but tomorrow you
should come wearing those.
Okay, got it.
Now, the first thing I need
you to do every morning
is punch me in the stomach
because I'm a bad person.
Is this a trick?
It's the furthest thing
from a trick. Go ahead.
And it should be pretty hard,
I'm a worse person than you think.
Okay, that's really good.
Now I need you to call
Time Warner about my cable bill.
All right, this one is for
all the mommies out there.
This is what we're
really saying when we're crying.
♪ Please put some
butt paste on my button ♪
♪ Butt paste on my button ♪
♪ Smear it on my button
for the fire down below ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, butt
paste on my button ♪
♪ Butt paste on my button ♪
♪ Need it on my button 'cause it ♪
♪ Cools and quells me so. ♪
♪ Stay away, stay away ♪
♪ From the big kid
in the baby swing. ♪
♪ There's a little metal box ♪
♪ At the top of the stairs ♪
♪ In the back of the closet ♪
♪ And a tiny little key ♪
♪ That's hidden in a book ♪
♪ In the drawer with the socks ♪
♪ And I know how to use it ♪
♪ To open up the box ♪
♪ And that's where the gun is. ♪
♪ ♪
You know, I talk a lot of smack,
but at the end of the day,
these guys are pros.
Even Broken Arm Coyote with Washboard.
Hey, let's keep this party rolling.
I'll go get us another badly-scratched
plastic pitcher of soda.
Ugh, finally, he's doing
something useful.
What? What do you mean?
Nothing. It's just,
you write all the songs,
you've got a better
voice, you've got the sweet bod...
Oh, my God, babe.
Plus, you've got all the cool
catchphrases like "damn you all"
or "what the dude" or whatever.
Uh, it-it's "deuce." But, uh,
but yeah, you're-you're
right, it... I-I do.
Does it-does it sound through the mic
like I'm saying
"dude"? Should it be "dude"?
Meanwhile, everyone thinks
Brian is the star of the group.
Who thinks that?
I don't know. I'm just saying,
after every show, the fans
are always petting Brian,
and not you.
No one's allowed to
pet me. It's illegal.
I just hate to see Brian
getting all the attention
that you deserve.
You should really watch your back.
Wow, it's hard to believe
Brian would betray me.
I mean, he was there for
me when I hit rock bottom.
See, Brian?
That's a rock bottom.
Thanks for being here for that.
Now get out of here, we're about
to drink some Chardonnay.
Chris, could you please get
Hannah a thank-you basket
and schedule her next appointment?
I'd like to see her again in two weeks.
Of course. Mr. Quagmire can fit in you
at 3:00 a week from Thursday.
That works.
And you know to fast the night before?
Yup.
And would you like to leave
your panties in the fishbowl
for a chance to win a free lunch?
Good luck.
When you gonna do that drawing anyway?
Oh, there's no drawing, I just
like smelling the bowl.
You know, you're doing
a great job, Chris.
Why don't you jerk
the rest of the day off.
Man, this is the best job ever.
And to think I almost took
that pop-up restaurant gig.
- Hi, you hungry?!
- Aah!
Check, check, Malia.
Check, Obama.
Check, check, check, Malia, Obama.
All right, that's a creepy mic check.
Let's just do a quick
run-through of "Little Brother."
♪ I want a little brother ♪
♪ On second thought ♪
♪ I think I'd ♪
♪ Kill him dead. ♪
Could-could we just cut Brian's mic?
His humming sounds like
my table's ready at Chili's.
Stewie, what the hell is your problem?
I'll tell you what my problem
is: I'm doing all the work
and you're just riding my coattails.
What are you talking about?
I'm just as big a part
of this group as you are.
Oh, really? You're writing about
all your authentic baby experiences?
You asked me to do this with you.
Why you being such a dick?
Because I lost the baby!
What was that?
I don't know, he saw that
in a movie or something.
Brian, this seems as good a time as any.
I think it's time to talk about
your future with the band.
Are you serious?
You're actually
kicking me out of the band?
Not at all. In fact,
I think you and I
should kick Stewie out.
And I'll take his place.
- What?
- Bring out the snakes!
Does he just come to all of our shows?
So, you want to fire Stewie
and be Red Shirt Blue Shirt with me?
Absolutely.
You're the whole reason
the fans even like the band.
Kids love dogs.
Besides, we've both seen
what Stewie's become:
an impossible diva.
Yeah, but he's my friend.
Yeah, well, your friend
has been talking about
kicking you out of the band.
Wait, what? He has?
And I don't know if
you've considered this,
but the clock is ticking
on Stewie's cuteness.
Huh. I guess you're right.
I mean, I wouldn't be
surprised if he ends up
looking like an exact
mash-up of Lois and Peter.
Groceries.
Hey. I had a thought about
our costumes for today's show.
I could wear a shirt
that's both red and blue,
and you can do spin art
with all the wussy kids
who are afraid to go on rides.
Yeah? Well, how about this, Stewie?
- You're fired.
- Pardon?
That's right. Olivia's
taking your place in the band.
You are looking at the new
Red Shirt Blue Shirt.
What the dude? Uhp, you know
what, "deuce" was right.
Come on, Brian. You and I
should probably rehearse.
We've got a show in 20 minutes.
Fine, go ahead! It's
not gonna be the same!
Like Cheers wasn't the same when
they brought in Kirstie Alley.
Norm!
No, I'm-I'm Rebecca.
Meg, do you know how
to use Microsoft Excel?
Yeah. I'm actually pretty good.
Yeah, you would. Dork.
But I do need to make that
spreadsheet or I'm fired.
Oh, my God.
Peter, our dishwasher
is full of sex toys.
Oh, yeah, Chris put those in there.
It's for his job. He's
workin' for Quagmire now.
He's washing sex toys for Quagmire?
Not just that. He also takes pictures
of Quagmire's genitals
to track sore growth.
So, brace yourself when you open iPhoto.
It's on the "Griffin Family" account.
Peter, my parents have access to that.
What's wrong with this worm?
And you knew about this?
How could you let him
do this disgusting stuff?
What? You're the one who
wanted Chris to get a job.
Yeah, like mowing lawns
or trimming bushes.
Oh, he's doing one of those.
That's it.
I'm calling Quagmire right now
and putting an end to this.
You have reached Glenn Quagmire.
Neither he nor his assistant
is available.
To schedule a liaison, press one.
To cancel a liaison, press two.
If you're calling to report
a pregnancy, please fill out
our online form, and we will
mail you a check for $180.
Thank you, and have a giggity day.
Chris, this is your mother.
Get these dildos out of the dishwasher.
♪ When everybody's gone to sleep ♪
♪ And you've said good night moon ♪
♪ There's plenty of
noise still coming ♪
♪ From Mommy and Daddy's room ♪
♪ Oh, Daddy says
"please", Mommy says "no" ♪
♪ Daddy says "come
on", Mommy says "whoa" ♪
♪ Daddy goes... , Mommy goes "ow" ♪
♪ Daddy says "I'm
done", Mommy goes "wow" ♪
STEWIE, BRIAN & OLIVIA: ♪
Daddy rolls over and falls asleep ♪
♪ Mommy drinks wine in the dark. ♪
Thank you, Quahog.
That was great. They loved us.
Yeah, I guess, but did
you see what I saw?
That kid with the cane?
Yeah, what do you think
is wrong with him?
No, Stewie was out there.
- So?
We're singing a song he wrote.
This whole thing was his idea.
Brian, don't mess this up.
We've got a good thing going.
I-I hate to tell
you this, but I'm afraid
Red Shirt Blue Shirt is done.
I can't do this. I'm out.
I don't care. I don't need you.
I can get a hundred dogs
to fit that stupid blue shirt.
You're a monster.
Like Frankenstein, when
he became a loan officer.
So, I'm looking for money
to open a small business.
We plan to sell antique lamps.
Handmade blankets.
And pitchforks.
Chris, there you are. We need to talk.
What, are you walkin' a horse?
Did Quagmire get a horse?
Oh no, here we go.
I want a horse!
Peter, it's not a horse.
Chris, what the hell is that?
Oh, this is Mr. Quagmire's horse gimp.
What is a "horse gimp"?
It's a sexual fetishist
who derives erotic pleasure
from dressing in horse-themed
leather gear.
Want to see me feed him a carrot?
- Absolutely not.
- Hell yes.
Chris, this is no job for a teenage boy.
You have to quit right now.
I can't quit. I'm actually
good at this job.
Plus, I'm making decent money.
You could work at the pharmacy.
Quiet, Triscuit!
Ooh, hook me to the plow!
Chris, I have $1,100 in a
paint can in the garage.
Just take that, and we'll
never speak of this again.
Okay.
Great. Now let's all go home.
Well, that's what I get
for horsing around.
Ah, your joke wasn't funny enough.
Stewie?
Oh, hello, Brian.
I'm here to apologize.
And to let you know I quit the band.
You did?
Yes. It's nothing without you.
You were the band.
Those were your songs.
And I'm sorry if I
let Olivia manipulate me.
I guess she manipulated both of us.
There's just something about her
flat chest and muscular legs.
Look, I never should've
treated you the way I did.
I suppose I didn't
treat you so well either.
So, what do you say? Can
we put this all behind us
and go back to the way things were?
Of course we can.
Hey, I wonder if she's
gonna keep the band going.
Probably. She told me
she was just gonna
replace me with another dog.
Yes, but who?
I don't know. Probably some dog
neither you or I have ever met.
All right, listen up,
you little pieces of garbage.
This song's about gettin'
heartburn from baked clams.
And other kid stuff.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru